export const reactQuestionsLessons = [
  {
    language:"English",
    id: 1,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "My daughter said I should take my umbrella, and _ too. While I was out it started pouring with rain.",
        options: ["just as well", "just as good", "just as lucky"],
        correctAnswer: "just as well",
      },
      {
        question: " I can't promise he'll listen to me and change his mind, but I'll _.",
        options: ["see what I can do", "see that I may do", "see what I will do"],
        correctAnswer: "see what I can do",
      },
      {
        question: " I moved to New York in 2010, and my life has been great _.",
        options: ["ever after", "ever since", "ever more"],
        correctAnswer: "ever since",
      },
      {
        question: "My friends don't believe in life after death. They say there's _ as heaven and hell.",
        options: ["no true thing", "no real thing", "no such thing"],
        correctAnswer: "no such thing",
      },
      {
        question: "I know you don't really like basketball, but we got the tickets for free so we _ go.",
        options: ["should as well", "must as well", "may as well"],
        correctAnswer: "may as well",
      },
      {
        question: "Your family will always be there to help you, _.",
        options: ["no matter what", "no matter which", "no matter that"],
        correctAnswer: "no matter what",
      },
      {
        question: " I'm cutting down on alcohol, so _ I'm only drinking light beer.",
        options: ["from now on", "for now on", "since now on"],
        correctAnswer: "from now on",
      },
      {
        question: "It's often said that there's a _ between genius and madness.",
        options: ["a thick line", "a fine line", "a long line"],
        correctAnswer: "a fine line",
      },
      {
        question: " In the village where I grew up, everyone survived by helping _ through the hard times.",
        options: ["one other", "one or other", "one another"],
        correctAnswer: "one another",
      },
      {
        question: "There's only one diving board, but if we _ diving everyone will have plenty of dives.",
        options: ["take goes", "take turns", "take tries"],
        correctAnswer: "take turns",
      }
    ]
  }, 
  {
    language:"English",
    id: 2,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Which is produced by insects?",
        options: ["fruit", "honey", "poultry"],
        correctAnswer: "honey",
      },
      {
        question: "If something is edible, it can be",
        options: ["very delicious", "easily cooked", "safely eaten"],
        correctAnswer: "safely eaten", 
      },
      {
        question: "Before the development of agriculture, what did people hunt?",
        options: ["fruits and seeds", "dairy foods", "animals and birds"],
        correctAnswer: "animals and birds",
      },
      {
        question: "Before the development of agriculture, what did people gather?",
        options: ["fruits and seeds", "dairy foods", "animals and birds"],
        correctAnswer: "fruits and seeds",
      },
      {
        question: "Agriculture developed when people began cultivating",
        options: ["edible plants", "wild animals", "meat and eggs"],
        correctAnswer: "edible plants",
      },
      {
        question: "Which word could be defined as an edible seed that grows in a long seed pod?",
        options: ["nut", "bean", "grain"],
        correctAnswer: "bean",
      },
      {
        question: "What are seeds from grasses such as wheat, rice and millet called?",
        options: ["food seeds", "grains", "beans"],
        correctAnswer: "grains",
      },
      {
        question: "What do poultry farmers usually raise?",
        options: ["eggs", "chickens", "feathers"],
        correctAnswer: "chickens",
      },
      {
        question: "Which are raised for their milk?",
        options: ["dairy cows", "dairy foods", "beef cattle"],
        correctAnswer: "dairy cows",
      },
      {
        question: "Which type of food does not always have a hard outer shell?",
        options: ["nuts", "seafood", "shellfish"],
        correctAnswer: "seafood",
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    language:"German",
    id: 3,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is 'to write'?",
        options: ["Schreiben", "Schlange", "Schule"],
        correctAnswer: "Schreiben",
      },
      {
        question: "What is 'Wednesday'?",
        options: ["Mittwoch", "Donnerstag", "Mittwock"],
        correctAnswer: "Mittwoch", 
      },
      {
        question: "Is Sunday the English for 'Samstag'?",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "How do you say 6:30?",
        options: ["Halb Sechs", "Halb Sieben", "Halb Acht"],
        correctAnswer: "Halb Sieben",
      },
      {
        question: "How do you say 6:45?",
        options: ["Viertel vor Sieben", "Viertel nach Sechs", "Viertel vor Sechs"],
        correctAnswer: "Viertel vor Sieben",
      },
      {
        question: "Is 'toll' the German for 'great'?",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Is 'Gro√üvater' the German for Grandfather?",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "How do you say 'It does me sorrow' (i.e.'I'm sorry.')?",
        options: ["Es tut mir leid", "Er ist nicht sehr gut", "Ich bin sieben Jahre alt"],
        correctAnswer: "Es tut mir leid",
      },
      {
        question: "The words 'welche' and 'welcher' ask 'Which?' .",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is Deutsch for the word 'with'?",
        options: ["Mit", "Und", "Wie"],
        correctAnswer: "Mit",
      },
    ]
  },

  {
    language:"German",
    id: 4,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "True or False'Tag' is the German for 'day'.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Select the missing word -Wir haben eine kleine Katze _ ein klein Hund.",
        options: ["Vor", "Und", "Aber"],
        correctAnswer: "Und", 
      },
      {
        question: "Which sentence is correct way of asking, 'Will you come with me?'",
        options: ["Wollen Sie mir kommen mit?", "Wollen Sie kommen mit mir?", "Wollen Sie mit mir kommen?"],
        correctAnswer: "Wollen Sie mit mir kommen?",
      },
      {
        question: "Translate -Wo wohnst du?",
        options: ["What's you name?", "Where do you live?", "How are you going?"],
        correctAnswer: "Where do you live?",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of these words means yesterday in German?",
        options: ["Morgen", "Heute", "Gestern"],
        correctAnswer: "Gestern",
      },
      {
        question: "The following sentence is logical -'Ich komme aus Tennis'.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Wie alt bist du?",
        options: ["Basket ball", "15", "Pizza"],
        correctAnswer: "15",
      },
      {
        question: "How do you say 'Please'?",
        options: ["Bitte", "Danke", "Tolle!"],
        correctAnswer: "Bitte",
      },
      {
        question: "Wie viel kostet das?",
        options: ["How cold is it?", "How far is that?", "How much does this cost?"],
        correctAnswer: "Gestern",
      },
      {
        question: "You could drink 'ein Glas Wasser'. True or false? ",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
    ]
  }
];